You call. They'll answer.
Talk to Me is a horror film directed by Michael Philippou.
When a group of friends discover how to conjure spirits using an embalmed hand, they become hooked on the
new thrill, until one of them goes too far and unleashes terrifying supernatural forces.
Mia, played by Sophie Wilde.
Jade, played by Alexandra Jensen.
Riley, played by Joe Bird.
Daniel, played by Otis Dhanji.
Sue, played by Miranda Otto.
Hayley, played by Zoe Terakes.
Talk to Me is a 2022 Australian supernatural horror film directed by Danny and Michael Philippou in their feature
directorial debuts and written by Danny Philippou and Bill Hinzman, based on a concept by Daley Pearson.
It stars Sophie Wilde, Alexandra Jensen, Joe Bird, Otis Dhanji, Miranda Otto, Zoe
Terakes, Chris Alosio, Marcus Johnson, and Alexandria Steffensen.
The film follows a group of teenagers discovering they can contact
spirits using a mysterious severed and embalmed hand.
Talk to Me premiered at the Adelaide Film Festival on 30 October 2022, and was released by Maslow Entertainment, Umbrella
Entertainment, and Ahi Films in Australia on 27 July 2023 and by A24 in the United States the following day.
The film received positive reviews from critics and grossed $92 million worldwide against a
production budget of $4.5 million, becoming A24's highest-grossing horror film.
At the 13th AACTA Awards, it won eight awards including the Best Film, the Philippou brothers won
for Best Direction and Best Original Screenplay, and Wilde won for Best Actress.
The film explores themes of suicide, trauma,
possession, female friendship, addiction.
The tone is dark.